<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dakota M. Gallimore</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <string name="brief_bio_description">Software Engineer. Android Developer. DevOps Advocate. Avid Coffee Drinker. Microservice Fanatic. Gamer. Global Entrepreneur. Content Creator. Outdoors Lover. Taco Destroyer.</string>
    <string name="about_me">I\'m Dakota Gallimore, a super passionate full-stack Software Engineer and go getter. I bring a unique blend of business and Software Engineering into the cloud-based development world. Having a vast background allows me to tackle every aspect of the software development life-cycle, from client relationship to scalable software. Never content with my current knowledge, I work to stay up on industry trends and technologies, pushing my skills to the limit. I\'m currently pursuing a career in scalable microservices with my next certifications geared towards the Kubernetes Administrator and Google Cloud Engineer Certifications.</string>
    <string name="personality">Passionate full-stack programmer that loves coffee. I\'m considered outgoing by my peers with a good sense of humor. I\'m also highly creative and not afraid of a whiteboard. Being a detailed oriented person, I\'m capable of formulating detailed designs at all layers, large and small. I tend to favor OOD principles and black box design as they allow for clean design and well defined software implementations. I\'m always in search of expanding my knowledge and prefer to take on rolls that have never been done before as the challenge excites me.</string>
    <string name="mission">My mission is simple, to join revolutionary teams in creating revolutionary software.</string>
    <string name="story">During college, I did not know what I wanted to do, other than programming. About two years into college I found my passion, mobile programming. At the time, our teachers had the students creating DOS programs, I wanted to create something someone would use, then I found Android. From there I took it upon myself to learn Android and created tons of apps to help me with them. I loved it. Then as I was prepping to launch my first app (an emotional roller coaster for sure) I had something hit me. If every app developer contributed a dollar to charity we could solve world hunger, which lead me to pursue Dreams.Build a Rewards-based crowdfunding platform focused around giving back. At the start of 2017 I launched in 23 countries, helping companies define their technology offerings, putting my Software Engineering and client relationship skills to the test. As 2017 came to a close, I began work at 1901Group, where we pioneered transforming legacy Oracle systems into microservice offerings. Since then I\'ve been a major advocate for all things Kubernetes or microservice oriented.</string>

    <string name="spinner_prompt">About me, but you can explore more</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Huh.. I missed a fragment, please try restarting the app.</string>
</resources>
